You faked it
You used hormones to fake it
Do you know how much money I lost
Boss, I was wrong
I really was wrong
Please spare me this once
Spare you
I'm calling the police
You cost me millions
I'll put you in jail
No
I can't go to jail
Grab him
Don't let him get away
Let go of me, Lewes
Save me
I know I was wrong
Now you're scared
It's too late
I paid you a high salary
Not because you're so capable
But because I never mistreat my employees
But you
You took my kindness for granted
And backstabbed me
I didn't kick you while you were down
That's already merciful enough
You two
One is evil
The other is stupid
Ending up like this today
You brought it upon yourselves
Mr. Walter
Let's go to my place and take a look
Let's go
I don't want to stay in this dump
For another second
Bad luck
Quick call an ambulance
Daniel is completely ruined now
It's karma
If he hadn't driven Lewes away back then
Would it come to this today